Clement F. Haynsworth Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- United States Court of Appeals File, 1955-1989 (Box 6-201)
  - Case File, 1956-1989 (Box 7-159)
    - 1963 October term
      - United States v. Baker, No. 9455
      - Lilly v. John Roane, Inc., No. 9456
      - American Casualty Co. v. Smith, No. 9457
      - Johnson v. United States, No. 9523
    - 1964 October term
      - Jones v. Rivers, No. 9158
      - Davis v. North Carolina, No. 9256
      - United States v. Crim, No. 9271
      - Carrington v. Civil Aeronautics Bd., No. 9316
      - United States v. Dillinger, No. 9366
      - United States v. Tucker, No. 9458
      - Bradley v. School Bd. of Richmond, No. 9471
      - Lawson v. Commissioner, No. 9491
      - Spaulding v. Anchor Motor Freight, No. 9492
      - Carey v. Foster, No. 9502
      - United States v. Southern Ry. Co., No. 9515
      - Hastings v. Mann, No. 9524
      - Nelson v. Victory Elec. Works, No. 9535
      - Koontz v. Celebrezze, No. 9553
      - Outing v. North Carolina, No. 9565
      - Giannakouros v. Oriental Tanker Corp., No. 9591
      - Starke v. United States, No. 9592
      - Greene v. S.S. Invicta, No. 9605
      - Barnes v. Sind, No. 9608
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Kotarides Baking Co., No. 9610
      - Cook v. Republic Steel Corp., No. 9615
      - Gibbs v. Blackwelder, No. 9616
      - Royal Indem. Co. v. Aetna Ins. Co., No. 9621
      - Gilliam v. School Bd. of Hopewell, No. 9625
      - Bowditch v. Buncombe County Bd. of Educ., No. 9628
      - Nesbit v. Statesville City Bd. of Educ., No. 9632
      - North River Ins. Co. v. Connecticut Fire Ins. Co., No. 9670
      - Flynn v. Kalb, No. 9683
      - Felder v. Harnett County Bd. of Educ., No. 9695
      - Norris Mfg. Co. v. R. E. Darling Co., No. 9699
      - United States v. Walker, No. 9710
      - McGann v. United States Marshal, No. 9725
      - Gadsden v. Fripp, No. 9761
      - Wagoner v. United States, No. 9803
      - Brown v. County School Bd. of Frederick County, No. 9825
      - Cooper Agency v. McLeod, No. 9871
      - Imperial Furniture Co. v. Piedmont Aviation, No. 9888
      - Brewer v. School Bd. of Norfolk, No. 9898
      - Thomas v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 9934
      - McManus v. Midland Valley Lumber Co., No. 9937
      - Brown v. Brough, No. 9964
    - 1965 October term
      - Hall v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 8592
      - Baines v. City of Danville, No. 9080
      - Virginia v. Wallace, No. 9462 (Box 15)
      - United States v. Talbert, No. 9525
      - Pinehurst, Inc. v. Schlamowitz, No. 9547
      - Virginia v. Morris, No. 9587
      - Hawkins v. North Carolina Dental Soc'y, No. 9612
      - Glass v. United States, No. 9636
      - Shelton v. Jones, No. 9651
      - Frye v. Celebrezze, No. 9666
      - Estate of Bryan v. Commissioner, No. 9676
      - Goodson v. Peyton, No. 9697
      - United States v. Smith, No. 9712
      - Loewy Drug Co. v. United States, No. 9731
      - Parke, Davis & Co. v. Health Cross Stores, No. 9733
      - Tincher v. Boles, No. 9736
      - Snider v. Peyton, No. 9742
      - Kalopodes v. Federal Reserve Bank, No. 9744
      - Reickauer v. Peyton, No. 9777
      - Sykes v. Virginia, No. 9793
      - United States v. Slaughter, No. 9800
      - United States v. White, No. 9809
      - Williams v. United States, No. 9840
      - Tenney v. A. B. & W. Transit Co., No. 9855
      - Hayes v. Peyton, No. 9878
      - United States v. Hall, No. 9880
      - Medomsley Steam Shipping Co. v. Elizabeth River Terminals, No. 9947
      - White v. Pepersack, No. 9971
      - Pokrinchak v. Holiday House Motel, No. 9978
      - United States v. Goss, No. 9996
      - Connorton v. Harbor Towing Corp., No. 9998
      - Ohio Casualty Ins. Co. v. Pennsylvania Nat'l Ins. Co., No. 10018
      - Morris v. South Carolina, No. 10023
      - Boddie v. Weakley, No. 10059
      - Hayden v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 10061
      - North Carolina v. Hawkins, No. 10062
      - Aldridge v. Roberts, No. 10066
      - United States v. Williams, No. 10080
      - Tackett v. Celebrezze, No. 10096
      - Stevens v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 10098
      - Federated Mut. Implement and Hardware Ins. Co. v. Gupton, No. 10151
      - Hart v. Wilkins, No. 10174
      - Griffin v. County School Bd., Prince Edward County, No. 10191
      - Smallwood v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 10205
      - United States v. Diodati, No. 10210
      - Humphries v. McCrory-McLellan Stores, No. 10223
      - Tucker v. Peyton, No. 10246
      - Freehill v. Benn, No. 10259
      - Flota Maritima Browning De Cuba v. Snobl, No. 10263
      - Haney v. Woodward & Lothrop, Inc., No. 10272
      - Horne v. Peyton, No. 10273
      - Langley Park Apartments v. Commissioner, No. 10283
      - Golding v. Celebrezze, No. 10287
      - United States v. Ard, No. 10289
      - Bullock v. Celebrezze, No. 10305
      - White v. United States, No. 10310
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Webb Furniture Corp., No. 10311
      - United States v. Henson, No. 10329
      - Patterson v. City of Newport News, No. 10333
      - Jones v. United States, No. 10339
      - United States v. Keller, No. 10345
      - United States v. Pennell, No. 10348
      - Armwood v. Brough, No. 10377
      - Utsey v. Southern R.R., No. 10378
      - United States v. Kincaid, No. 10402
      - Atha v. Gardner, No. 10454
      - United States v. Ardner, No. 10458
      - United States v. Sutton, No. 10471
      - Coleman v. Peyton, No. 10473
      - Crawford v. Bailey, No. 10477
      - United States v. Muhammad, No. 10480
      - United States v. Foster, No. 10509
      - Donohue v. Maryland Casualty Co., No. 10518
      - Porter v. Peyton, No. 10535
    - 1966 October term
      - Jacobs v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 9564
      - Casella v. Norfolk and W. Ry., No. 9716
      - Commissioner v. Mary Archer W. Morris Trust, No. 9837
      - Syer v. United States, No. 9850
      - United States v. Moran Towing and Transp. Co., No. 9867
      - Kelly v. Raese, No. 9918
      - Wright v. Masonite Corp., No. 9940
      - Stevens v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 10005
      - McClure v. United States Lines Co., No. 10014
      - Island Creek Coal Co. v. Commissioner, No. 10028
      - Ballwanz v. Jarka Corp., No. 10067
      - Baltimore v. Renegotiation Bd., No. 10090
      - United Steelworkers v. Bagwell, No. 10130
      - Rambo v. Peyton, No. 10153
      - Lambert v. Celebrezze, No. 10160
      - Swann v. Charlotte-Mecklenburg Bd. of Educ., No. 10207
      - Weber v. Rivers, No. 10358
      - Perkins v. Peyton, No. 10504
      - United States v. Hinton, No. 10586
      - United States v. Claimant of 392 copies of Exclusive, No. 10600
      - Sims v. Berkeley Loan and Thrift Corp., No. 10603
      - United States v. Bencon Constr. Co., No. 10607
      - Munson v. Murphy, No. 10615
      - United States v. Banks, No. 10628
      - Intertype Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 10636
      - Kirby v. Atlantic Coast R.R., No. 10641
      - Sanderlin v. Martin, No. 10642
      - United States v. Raybon, No. 10647
      - Murray v. Commissioner, No. 10670
      - Reese v. Commissioner, No. 10686
      - United States v. Wallace, No. 10712
      - Tracy v. Robbins, No. 10718
      - Green v. County School Bd. of New Kent County, No. 10792 (Box 16)
      - Bowman v. County School Bd. of Charles City County, No. 10793
      - Maryland Nat'l Bank v. Tower, No. 10797
      - United States v. Potomac News Co., No. 10798
      - United States v. Barrier, No. 10805
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Weston and Brooker Co., No. 10835
      - Monette v. Commissioner, No. 10839
      - Gregory v. Town of Pageland, No. 10858
      - Wehrle v. Brooks, No. 10900
      - Macloskie v. Royal Indem. Co., No. 10901
      - Allstate Ins. Co. v. McNeill, No. 10912
      - Outing v. North Carolina, No. 10926
      - Wansley v. Virginia, No. 10930
      - Yates v. Peyton, No. 10932
      - Wetherbee v. Norfolk, Baltimore & Carolina Line, No. 10935
      - Sims v. United States, No. 10937
      - United States v. Smith, No. 10959
      - Paige v. Ross, No. 10960
      - United States v. Coltraine, No. 10961
      - Walker v. North Carolina, No. 10962
      - Moore v. Island Creek Coal Co., No. 10963
      - Wilson v. Ohio River Co., No. 10982
      - United States v. Cosby, No. 10990
      - United States v. Hailey, No. 11001
      - United Bond and Mortgage Corp. v. Crown Cent. Petroleum Corp., No. 11007
      - Cobb v. Clark, No. 11008
      - United States v. Black, No. 11026
      - United States v. Hayes, No. 11032
      - Arey v. Peyton, No. 11037
      - United States v. Hemphill, No. 11047
      - Autry v. Crumpler, No. 11054
      - United States v. Edlin, No. 11061
      - Tyndall v. Gardner, No. 11084
      - Wade v. Peyton, No. 11110
      - Massey v. Gardner, No. 11131
      - United States v. Malry, No. 11144
      - United States v. Nimmo, No. 11156
      - United States v. Bloombaum, No. 11161
      - Tompa v. Peyton, No. 11170
      - Collins v. Collins, No. 11180
      - Harrold v. Coble, No. 11199
      - Crouch v. Gardner, No. 11214
      - Thacker v. Peyton, No. 11217
      - Valentine Waterways Corp. v. Tug Choptank, No. 11229
      - In re Crouse, No. 11231
      - Reynolds v. Gardner, No. 11261
      - Farrow v. Grace Lines, Inc., No. 11265
      - Haughton Elevator Co. v. Donata Corp., No. 11272
      - Abshire v. Gardner, No. 11274
      - United States v. 60,000 copies of magazines, No. 11275
      - Kelly v. Chillag, No. 11285
      - Virginia Elec. Power Co. v. System Council No. U-1, Int'l Bhd. of Elec. Workers, No. 11300
    - 1967 October term
      - Leonhardt v. United States, No. 10165
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Sehon Stevenson & Co., No. 10189
      - Avery v. Oosting, No. 10323
      - Ransburg Electro-Coating Corp. v. Ionic Electrostatic, No. 10347
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. S. S. Logan Packing Co., No. 10355
      - General Steel Prods. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 10543
      - Crawford v. Bounds, No. 10981
      - United States v. Wilson, No. 10991
      - H. B. Agsten & Sons v. Huntington Trust & Sav. Bank, No. 11028
      - United States v. Weaver, No. 11119
      - Snider v. Peyton, No. 11140
      - Heine v. Raus, No. 11195
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Gissel Packing Co., No. 11228
      - Brown v. Gardner, No. 11354
      - United States v. Hodge, No. 11367
      - United States v. Parks, No. 11381
      - United States v. Boney, No. 11384
      - Thacker v. Gardner, No. 11393
      - Ray v. Gardner, No. 11419
      - United States v. Shue, No. 11442
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Electro Motive Mfg. Co., No. 11447
      - United States v. Martin, No. 11461
      - United States v. Markowitz Bros., No. 11498
      - United States v. Sisk, No. 11512
      - United States v. Lawson, No. 11517
      - Darlington Mfg. Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 11554
      - Manderacchi v. United States, No. 11574
      - United States v. Campbell, No. 11584
      - United States v. Sox, No. 11622
      - United States v. Koon, No. 11623
      - United States v. Whitaker, No. 11645
      - United States v. McKoy, No. 11650
      - Hammerman v. Arlington Fed. Sav. & Loan Ass'n, No. 11663
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Heck's, Inc., No. 11671
      - Blaw-Knox Co. v. Hartsville Oil Mill, No. 11680
      - United States v. Pierce, No. 11706
      - Brewer v. School Bd. of Norfolk, No. 11782 (Box 17)
      - United States v. Law, No. 11786
      - Coppedge v. Franklin County Bd. of Educ., No. 11794
      - Brown v. Fogel, No. 11802
      - United States v. Vickers, No. 11815
      - United States v. Van Horn, No. 11824
      - Maryland Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Co. v. Baker-Whitely Towing Co., No. 11826
      - Mills v. Mealey, No. 11896
      - Southern Materials Co. v. Merritt-Chapman & Scott Corp., No. 11921
      - United States v. Harris, No. 11991
      - United States v. Owens, No. 12043
      - Buckingham v. United States, No. 12073
      - United States v. Coggins, No. 12085
      - Tenney v. A. B. & W. Transit Co., No. 12090
      - Owens v. Traynor, No. 12096
      - Roberts v. Commissioner, No. 12111
      - Roberts v. Gardner, No. 12121
      - Bradshaw v. Island Creek Coal Co., No. 12135
      - Poulter v. Commissioner, No. 12187
      - Morse v. Boswell, No. 12738
    - 1968 October term
      - Word v. North Carolina, No. 10765
      - McFalls v. Peyton, No. 11567
      - Roberts v. Fuquay Tobacco Bd. of Trade, No. 11583
      - Alford v. North Carolina, No. 11598
      - McCreight v. South Carolina, No. 11675
      - United States v. Clay, No. 11681
      - Satterfield v. Boles, No. 11689
      - Cost v. Coiner, No. 11695
      - Hewett v. North Carolina, No. 11772 (Box 18)
      - United States v. Wood, No. 11878
      - United States v. Furr, No. 11935
      - United States v. Kilgore, No. 12007
      - Miller v. Blalock, No. 12019
      - Pavement Salvage Co. v. Anderson's-Black Rock, No. 12020
      - Breaker Confections v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 12078
      - Wratchford v. S. J. Groves & Sons Co., No. 12140
      - United States v. Penny, No. 12173
      - Carter-Wallace, Inc. v. Gardner, No. 12200
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Kingwood Mining Co., No. 12291
      - United States v. Burgess, No. 12311
      - United States v. Fentress, No. 12318
      - Smith v. Peyton, No. 12357
      - United States v. Morton, No. 12364
      - United States v. Duke, No. 12414
      - United States v. Myers, No. 12444
      - United States v. Bully, No. 12458
      - Strouth v. Peyton, No. 12478
      - Ross v. Gardner, No. 12514
      - Blackhurst v. E. I. du Pont de Nemours and Co., No. 12523
      - Dinges v. Tate, No. 12574
      - United States v. Mitchell, No. 12617
      - Tempest v. United States, No. 12630
      - Middlebrooks v. Curtis Publishing Co., No. 12672
      - United States v. Parkway Towers, No. 12703
      - Coppedge v. United States, No. 12752
      - Chatham Mfg. Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 12790 (Box 19)
      - United States v. Cooley, No. 12874
      - Lester v. McFaddon, No. 12875
      - United States v. Adams, No. 12940
      - Schell v. Chesapeake & Ohio Ry., No. 12955
      - United States v. Berrigan, No. 12980
      - United States v. Bauguess, No. 12982
      - Sams v. Ohio Valley Gen. Hosp. Ass'n, No. 12983
      - United States v. Golden, No. 12987
      - United States v. Kirkman, No. 13010
      - United States v. Cass, No. 13047
      - United States v. Richardson, No. 13133
      - Dairyland Ins. Co. v. McGraw, No. 13138
      - United States v. Barker, No. 13155
      - Williams v. United States Dist. Court, No. 13206
      - Tug Raven v. Trexler, No. 13216
      - Rogers v. First Nat'l Bank, No. 13393
    - 1969 October term
      - Hewlett v. Barge Bertie, No. 12671
      - United States v. Palmer, No. 12877
      - Wilson v. North Carolina, No. 13339
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Reliable Coal Corp., No. 13367
      - Tidewater Patent Dev. v. Kitchen, No. 13391
      - Bellomy v. Union Concrete Pipe Co., No. 13512
      - Nichols v. Finch, No. 13526
      - J. A. Hackney & Sons v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 13572
      - Griffey v. Finch, No. 13600
      - United States v. McCloud, No. 13648
      - United States v. Payne, No. 13651
      - Varga v. United States, No. 13669
      - Piedmont Minerals Co. v. United States, No. 13677
      - McReynolds v. County School Bd. of Fairfax County, No. 13704
      - Atwell v. Retail Credit Co., No. 13727 (Box 20)
      - Murray v. Finch, No. 13731
      - Walutes v. Thorington Constr. Co., No. 13732
      - United States v. Swanson, No. 13765
      - United States v. Diggs, No. 13767
      - United States v. Greene, No. 13770
      - United States v. O'Dell, No. 13776
      - United States v. Canty, No. 13793
      - United States v. Starkey, No. 13806
      - United States v. Daniels, No. 13815
      - United States v. Dockery, No. 13818
      - United States v. Gray, No. 13845
      - United States v. Jones, No. 13862
      - Wuelfing v. Sears, Roebuck & Co., No. 13899
    - 1970 October term
      - Shiflett v. Virginia, No. 12355
      - Levine v. Peyton, No. 13127
      - United States v. Knupp, No. 13314
      - Sas cases, No. 13415
      - Anderson v. Finch, No. 13509
      - United States v. Harris, No. 13586
      - United States v. Edick, No. 13590
      - Iron City Sand & Gravel Div. v. West Fork Towing Corp., No. 13673 (Box 21)
      - Ralph v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 13757
      - Easley v. Finch, No. 13852
      - Duffy v. Gudger, No. 13891
      - United States v. Siegel, No. 13897
    - 1971 October term
      - Miller v. Perry, No. 13858
      - Kaufman v. Commissioner, No. 71-1358
      - United States v. Ross, No. 71-1371
      - United States v. Moore, No. 71-1385
      - Federal Land Bank v. Wood, No. 71-1389
      - United States v. Smith, No. 71-1404
      - Shaw v. United States, No. 71-1412
      - United States v. Shuford, No. 71-1424
      - Manns v. Koontz, No. 71-1458
      - United States v. Harris, No. 71-1460
      - United States v. Brown, No. 71-1483
      - Breman v. United States, No. 71-1504
      - Winburn v. United States, No. 71-1508
      - Bishop v. Richardson, No. 71-1524
      - United States v. Langley, No. 71-1553
      - Allen v. State Bd. of Educ. of N.C., No. 71-1563
      - United States v. Toler, No. 71-1625
      - United States v. DeBruhl, No. 71-1633
      - United States v. Lotty, No. 71-1700
      - United States v. Shorter, No. 71-1701 (Box 22)
      - United States v. Smith, No. 71-1730
      - Raulston v. Carolina-Caribbean Corp., No. 71-1735
      - United States v. Valentine, No. 71-1743
      - Groves v. Richardson, No. 71-1744
      - Buresch v. International Bhd. of Elec. Workers, Local 24, No. 71-1745
      - United States v. Payne, No. 71-1758
      - Carson v. American Sav. Life Ins. Co., No. 71-1801
      - Stubbs v. Hardee, No. 71-1847
      - United States v. Simmons, No. 71-1848
      - Lea v. Cone Mills Corp., No. 71-1852
      - United States v. Proffitt, No. 71-1854
      - United States v. Smith, No. 71-1899
      - Holt Mfg. Co. v. Federated Mut. Implement and Hardware Ins. Co., No. 71-1907
      - United States v. Pawlik, No. 71-1911
      - United States v. Sutherland, No. 71-1921
      - Capital Investors Co. v. Morrison, No. 71-1923
      - Walton v. Richardson, No. 71-1946
      - United States v. Moore, No. 71-1966
      - Hitchcock v. Laird, No. 71-1971
      - Johnson v. Richardson, No. 71-1972
      - Ranger Ins. Co. v. Lewis, No. 71-1986
      - Lyons v. Richardson, No. 71-1987
      - Calico Scallopo Corp. v. Willis Bros., No. 71-1998
      - United States v. Aiken, No. 71-2008
      - United States v. Evans, No. 71-2009
      - Long Mfg. Co. v. Lilliston Implement Co., No. 71-2016
      - Felts v. Seaboard Coast Line R.R., No. 71-2021
      - Road Materials v. Commissioner, No. 71-2048
      - Rederi A/B Soya v. Evergreen Marine Corp., No. 71-2050
      - United States v. Smygelski, No. 71-2052
      - Embrey v. Hampton, No. 71-2073
      - United States v. Harris, No. 71-2091
      - Edwards v. Flowers, No. 71-2129
      - Holt v. City of Richmond, No. 71-2185 (Box 23)
      - United States v. Henderson, No. 71-2197
      - United States v. Thomas, No. 71-2209
      - Mims v. Yarborough, No. 72-1013
      - United States v. Bittinger, No. 72-1020
      - Smith v. Commissioner, No. 72-1025
      - United States v. Echeverria, No. 72-1026
      - United States v. Vacca, No. 72-1090
      - United States v. Copas, No. 72-1110
      - United States v. Weidlein, No. 72-1139
      - Kennedy v. Wheeling-Pittsburgh Steel Corp., No. 72-1142
      - United States v. Marshall, No. 72-1168
      - Pilkerton v. United States, No. 72-1208
      - Hall's Motor Transit Co. v. Hartnett, No. 72-1214
      - United States v. Tate, No. 72-1252
      - United States v. Browder, No. 72-1270
      - Elmore v. United States, No. 72-1280
      - Falk v. Hodgson, No. 72-1289
      - United States v. Embry, No. 72-1359
      - McCain v. Abel, No. 72-1373
      - United States v. Braswell, No. 72-1392
      - United States v. Maners, No. 72-1396
      - United States v. Marchetti, No. 72-1586
      - United States v. Bremer, No. 72-1657
    - 1972 October term
      - Cox v. United States, No. 71-1384
      - Terry v. Superintendent, Field Unit #9, No. 71-1682 (Box 24)
      - Cohen v. Chesterfield County School Bd., No. 71-1707; (2 folders)
      - Blake v. National Research Assocs., No. 71-1708
      - White v. Brough, No. 71-1872
      - Thompson v. School Bd. of Newport News, No. 71-2032
      - United States v. White, No. 71-2219
      - Foy v. Bounds, No. 72-1003
      - United States v. Parrish, No. 72-1046
      - United States v. Teeter, No. 72-1182
      - Hodgson v. J. W. Lyles, Inc., No. 72-1222
      - United States v. Gurley, No. 72-1236
      - United States v. McCoy, No. 72-1254
      - McClung v. Ford Motor Co., No. 72-1257
      - Moody v. Albemarle Paper Co., No. 72-1267; (1 folder) (Box 25)
      - United States v. Figueroa, No. 72-1275
      - United States v. Bluett, No. 72-1367
      - Chitwood v. Feaster, No. 72-1404
      - Bigham v. Westinghouse Elec. Corp., No. 72-1414
      - Marston v. J. C. Penney Co., No. 72-1424
      - Early Settlers Ins. Co. v. International Serv. Ins. Co., No. 72-1469
      - Karborough v. Eastern Fin. Corp., No. 72-1503
      - United States v. Skeens, No. 72-1520
      - United States v. Biles, No. 72-1521
      - United States v. Baggett, No. 72-1548
      - Wray v. Hall, No. 72-1552
      - United States v. Williamson, No. 72-1621
      - Edwards v. Richardson, No. 72-1634
      - United States v. Sidella, No. 72-1636
      - United States v. Davis, No. 72-1674
      - Acorn Elec. Supply v. Powell Elec. Mfg., No. 72-1677
      - United States v. Webb, No. 72-1684
      - United States v. Fink, No. 72-1687
      - Moffitt v. Ross, No. 72-1720
      - Hodgson v. Bradley, No. 72-1732
      - United States v. Culpepper, No. 72-1735
      - United States v. Paurowski, No. 72-1770
      - United States v. Tidd, No. 72-1791
      - United States v. Malcolm, No. 72-1807
      - United States v. Diamond, No. 72-1834
      - United States v. Rocks, No. 72-1862 (Box 26)
      - United States v. Turner, No. 72-1882
      - United States v. Fane, No. 72-1889
      - United States v. Moore, No. 72-1896
      - Kopalko v. United States, No. 72-1908
      - United States v. Rosenfield, No. 72-2004
      - United States v. Downing, No. 72-2028
      - United States v. King, No. 72-2031
      - United States v. Morin, No. 72-2034
      - Gibbs v. Norfolk S. Ry., No. 72-2119
      - Vaughns v. Board of Educ., Prince George's County, No. 72-2129
      - Hogge v. United States, No. 72-2136
      - United States v. Carey, No. 72-2241
      - Metropolitan Life Ins. Co. v. United States, No. 72-2298
      - United States v. Ross, No. 72-2300
      - United States v. Bohannon, No. 72-2304
      - United States v. Bowen, No. 72-2349
      - Lee v. Walworth Valve Co., No. 72-2360
      - Slaughter v. Winston, No. 72-2371
      - Slade v. Smith, No. 72-2398
      - United States v. Shirley, No. 72-2417
      - United States v. Cain, No. 72-2456
      - United States v. Braud, No. 72-2506
      - Shole v. O'Donnell, No. 72-8021
      - Willis Bros. v. Ocean Scallops, No. 73-1021
      - Lusk v. United Ass'n of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing Indus., Local 540, No. 73-1065
      - United States v. Lomax, No. 73-1113
      - United States v. Tanner, No. 73-1123
      - Shumate v. Board of Educ., County of Jackson, No. 73-1139
      - United States v. Bennett, No. 73-1142
      - United States v. Lee, No. 73-1143